# Utkarsh Pandey

36/2/15 B Mohanpura, Idgah Agra Agra, Uttar Pradesh, 282001 8410106571 utkarsh.pandey170@gmail.com

# Summary

Customer service representative with over 4 years of experience in telephonic customer care, including sales, tech support, and customer care. Familiar with major customer service software, conflict resolution, and possess a positive attitude. Aiming to use proven skills to effectively fill the managerial role in your company.

### Education

**Kanpur University**, Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh Bachelor's of Science

Graduated - April 2017

# **Employment History**

**Serco Inc**, Agra, Uttar Pradesh *Customer service representative* 

May 2013 - October 2013

Working with Vodafone Qatar international process as a customer service Representative.

#### Wyndham Grand Hotel and Resorts, Agra, Uttar Pradesh

Guest relation Executive

October 2015 - February 2019

Working as Guest Relation Executive in Wyndham Grand Hotel and Resorts, Agra. Guest Relations Executive responsibilities include greeting clients as they arrive, coordinating their check-ins to assigned rooms and informing them about the hotel's facilities. ... Ultimately, you will manage guest services and our hotel's image by answering guests' requests and making sure our visitors are satisfied.

#### Weddingz.in, Chandigarh, Punjab

Venue Manager

April 2019 - Present

Working as a Venue Manager in Weddingz.in. A Venue Manager is the person in charge of a location or event space. This may be a hall, theatre, conference centre or hotel. Their main duty is to oversee activities and use of the facilities, which involves ensuring the venue is clean and all equipment is working.

## **Hobbies & Interests**

**Bike Riding:**The roar of the engine, the authority of the handlebars that rest beneath your fingers and the rush of adrenaline that fills your body when you whiz by motorists who slowly putt along on any highway:This is what transpires when riding. Feeling the wind blow through your hair and the power of cruising down a road with nothing surrounding you but the beauty of the outdoors is something many people adopt this time of year.

### **Professional Skills**

Customer service Expert
Management Expert

Microsoft office Intermediate

# Languages

English Hindi Punjabi